So what are we doing tomorrow?
Tomorrow,
- we'll start work at dawn.
- At what time?
We'll take off at 5:30am.
Right.
Taking off at 5:30am?
Oh, my gosh.
At 5:30am?
(Surprised at the very early time)
To take off at 5:30am,
we'll have to get up at 4:50am.
Oh, my goodness.
(It's their first time working at the crack of dawn.)
(They're already worried.)
(An early hour when the sun is just rising)
(What is waiting for them in the day ahead?)
I'm going to wash up and go to bed. I'm so tired.
Oh, goodness.
Right. We should turn this off.
- I'll set an alarm.
- What?
I'll set an alarm.
- But your alarm...
- You'll be woken up...
by my alarm anyway.
Your alarm will wake me up.
We have to wake up at 4:30am.
(Crying)
Sleep well, You Seok.
Sleep well.
Sleep tight.
(Goodnight, everyone.)
(The moon lights up the night sky.)
(Maegye Village is deep asleep.)
(The blue light of dawn slowly starts to appear.)
(Current time: 4:30am)
(The siblings aren't moving at all in the darkness.)
(The sound of the alarm cuts through the silence.)
(Yoon Seo got up first.)
Do you want to wash up first, Yoon Seo?
- Just my face. Just a minute.
- Okay.
(I'll go first and wash my face.)
(Having a hard time waking up so early in the morning)
We should stretch a bit, don't you think?
My body feels so slow.
Yoon Seo, you're so pretty right now. Stay still.
What are you talking about?
You can close your eyes.
(Unsure what to do)
(She has to get some pictures when Yoon Seo looks pretty.)
(Our Yoon Seo is so pretty, even when she's half awake.)
(Squirming around)
Am I pretty right now?
What?
I'm pretty right now too, right?
No?
Not in particular...
(Waiting expectantly)
Your face is super puffy.
(Even early in the morning, Jung Ah is firm.)
Yoon Seo, how do I look right now?
My beauty.
So lovely.
- You're the best, Yoon Seo.
- You look pretty.
What time is it now?
Let's see.
It's 5:03am. You need to get ready.
(Turning on the lights to really start getting ready)
You Seok.
(Sitting right up)
(Now everyone is up, including You Seok.)
I'll just wash my face here.
(Sun Young starts washing her face at the outdoor faucet.)
(Pretty thorough)
(Washing vigorously)
(Cleaning foam is a luxury.)
(She just roughly washes her face with water.)
(Wild Sun Young)
(Pushing her hair back)
There we go.
(Refreshed)
(Right as Sun Young finished her wild outdoor face cleanse, )
(You Seok comes out of the bathroom.)
How do I look, You Seok?
My face right now. Do I look great?
- Today?
- Yes.
- A six on the die.
What's "six on the die?"
- You know it, right, Yoon Seo?
- What?
When someone says, "You rolled a six today,"
- Yes.
- it means you look very pretty.
Okay, I got it.
- When you roll die, - You rolled die,
- six is the highest number.
- and you got a six.
(My appearance is a six on die?)
I rolled a six today.
(Feeling good)
Can you say, "D-Six?" too? Do people say that?
- No, they just say six on die.
- Okay.
She learned about shortening phrases,
and now she tries to shorten anything.
I got ready the quickest.
(Starting with our happy D-Six, )
(everyone is now ready to go to work.)
- Shall we get going?
- Yes.
(You Seok's choice for today's drive-to-work song)
(From now)
(You'll lose your smile, "Uphill" by Yoon Jong Shin)
We're going uphill right now.
(Look at this steep road)
(I love you, the one going to work with me)
(Wistful)
(Worried)
(You who chose tough work)
What is in store for us today?
(What sort of uphill road will they climb up today?)
(Meanwhile)
(This place has an oddly bleak air.)
(Hazardous materials storage)
(This is where the siblings are headed.)
(This place is full of mysterious fixtures.)
(A mysterious man appears.)
(He suspiciously stands in front of the mirror.)
(Sliding out his phone)
(Snap)
(Today's guest, Ji Jin Hee)
(Jin Hee is a master before-work mirror selfies.)
Since I took one, I should post it.
(Since I took one, I should post it on Instagram!)
(With his phone that opens up, )
(he's doing his daily routine.)
(Lips pursed in concentration)
I posted it.
What hashtag are you going to put?
"On the way to a new job?"
Oh, I should change it from "new" to "my other." Hold on.
I don't know how to change it.
I'll just post it as is.
(Giving up without hesitation)
This pine tree is beautiful.
Yes, the trees with straight trunks and branches at the top.
(Suddenly being impressed by pine trees)
Apparently, these are the pine trees that are native to Korea.
The ones with the straight trunks and the branches at the top.
Their lumber makes good building materials.
The bendy pine trees...
It must be hard for them to grow so closely packed together.
I think they need more space.
(Does he have some connection to pine trees?)
Oh, Mount Jiri...
Just breathing the air here feels healing.
What are you looking forward to today?
Jung Ah is such...
a good friend of mine.
I'm always happy to see Jung Ah.
(He came on the show to spend time with Jung Ah.)
How long have you known each other?
It's been over 20 years.
My first movie...
I filmed it with her.
We filmed another movie together after that as well.
Also, I was the MC...
at Jung Ah's wedding.
We always see each other...
at big events like weddings and funerals.
(He took a seat to share more information about Jung Ah.)
We were in Busan together for over seven months.
For 15 days...
One time, we had to wait 15 days to shoot our next scene.
(For some reason)
Jung Ah was in the next room.
You know what she was always doing? She was cleaning.
(She was cleaning!)
I mean, that's fine, but she cleans again the next day.
And the next day, and the next.
The day after that, she was washing all of the curtains.
Then, she flipped over all of the sofas to clean them.
She kept cleaning, saying it was nice to be clean.
She cleaned for 15 days.
(She's still the same 20 years later...)
I thought she was interesting.
(She's still the same 20 years later.)
(How will Jin Hee react when he meets the siblings?)
- Are they on their way?
- Pardon?
Are they on their way?
- We're going to Gwangyang.
- What is there?
Let's see. What's waiting for us 400m ahead?
- Is it field work?
(All they see outside of the window are green fields...)
I don't think it'll be field work.
They wouldn't send us all the way here for field work.
There are many fields back there too.
- Eel...
- But we did go one hour...
- to Geoje to harvest onions.
- In a moment, turn right.
Jung Ah, we did go.
(Jung Ah, they do send us out 1 hour for field work.)
We went for one hour.
Here?
(While they're all confused about what work they'll do today, )
(they drive into a spooky forest road.)
What could it be? I'm curious.
They're all wearing rain boots.
They're going to make us wear those.
They told us to wear these pants...
- so we can wear those boots.
- The boots that come up there.
- Thank you for driving.
- Have a good day.
We have to wear those rain boots.
It's eel.
Why are you hiding it?
Shall we go catch some eel?
- Shall we?
- Let's go.
(Will it really be eel?)
(The siblings follow the road.)
What could be here?
- There must be an eel farm there.
- Really?
(This is an eel farm?)
- They farm eels here.
- It has to be eel.
It has to be eel. Right?
Oh, but eels are...
This is a farm. They pull the water in from here.
Oh, my. This is going to be tough.
I really love eel, but an eel farm...
It must be hard to catch eels.
- So...
- Hey.
We have something to tell you about today's labor.
Okay.
There are instructions and precautions on the mirror.
Please go and take a look.
(Instructions?)
We have to catch eels with our bare hands?
- "Bare hands, bare feet..."
- Bare feet?
(On one side of the mirror)
(Safety Precautions, 1. You must work barehanded.)
(2. You must work barefooted.)
(Shocked)
- "You must work barehanded."
- Two.
- "You must work barefooted."
- Three.
"Keep a safe distance from each other."
- Four.
- "You cannot leave in the middle."
That sounds scary.
- Oh, my goodness!
- Oh, my!
(Oh, my goodness!)
(What in the world...)
- What was that?
- That really scared me.
(What in the world did they see?)
That's so scary.
- Oh, my goodness!
- Oh, my!
(Why is Ji Jin Hee in there?)
(30 minutes before the siblings arrived)
(The mirror he took a selfie in front of had a secret.)
Real mirrors, when you put your hand on them,
have some space between your hand and the reflection.
But with fake mirrors, your hand directly touches the reflection.
This is a fake mirror. It's a two-way mirror.
(At a glance, it looks like a normal mirror.)
This is well made.
(There's space behind the mirror.)
(Cozy)
(When the light is turned on, you can see inside.)
This will be fun.
(Already excited)
(And like that, he waited for the siblings to arrive.)
- Oh, gosh.
- That's so scary.
(That's how he appeared this way.)
(He even successfully scared his good friend, Jung Ah.)
(Super surprised)
(Our selfie master in the mirror)
- I thought it was a ghost.
- That really scared me.
(It's almost like a haunted house.)
- Oh, you!
Have you been well?
- Hello.
- This is my brother.
- This is Jin Hee.
- Hello.
- Jung Ah...
- I'm Kang You Seok.
What sort of system is this?
- Oh, my. Hello, Mr. Ji.
- That really scared me.
- You've never worked with them?
- No.
- We're meeting for the first time.
- Same for me.
He's one year older than me.
He's young and handsome, right?
I'm one year older but young and handsome? What is that?
I'm saying you look young.
Oh, that's why they put that here.
This glass...
- Was this custom-made?
- You said we had no budget.
- I see.
Spending our budget on this to scare us for a second...
- From Seoul?
- Oh, you made this?
- This whole thing?
- Yes.
It's so funny you got this custom-made.
- It's such a waste.
- We're so careful...
- with how we spend money.
- Exactly. We...
Do you know that?
- How to tell if it's real or fake?
- Yes.
If your hand and your hand in the reflection...
- touch each other, it's fake.
- Right.
- They do touch.
- What do you mean?
- Look at the mirror.
- When you put your hand here...
(The fingers are touching?)
- There's some space here.
- It's fake.
- Where is the space?
- This is fake.
This is fake. It's a fake mirror.
There's supposed to be a space...
the thickness of the mirror. About this much.
But it's not that.
- It's a mirror if it reflects.
- Right.
How do we catch eels with our bare hands?
(Meanwhile, You Seok is worried about the precautions.)
- Something we do...
- Maybe it's not eel, then.
- with our bare hands...
- It's not eel, then.
Why do we need to keep...
- a safe distance from each other?
- What is the reason?
It says they don't bite or harm.
It says they're small and slippery. It is eel.
But why do we have to work barehanded?
- You can't grab the eels, then.
- You can't.
- I think that's what they're after.
- I don't think it'll work.
I think he'll leave once they're all released...
- I think so too.
- It must be in here.
- So you two should...
- Here?
Oh, this should be easy.
I'm scared of eels.
- There's nothing inside.
- "Feed production..."
- I think it's over there.
I wonder what we're doing.
It's a very well-organized system.
What is this?
- I see.
- Is there also a field?
- Oh, my.
- There are also eggs.
- What is this?
- Over there?
(Oh, my gosh!)
- You can see the fish there, right?
- Look at the eels.
Those are eels?
(In the wide open field)
(Full of things powerfully squirming around)
(The siblings' second job, wild eel)
The eels you'll catch today...
were raised for five years in ocher...
and clean underground water that was changed out every day.
(In the ocher, live wild eels that grew up with nature)
We try to raise eels...
in open fields using natural means.
It takes about 4 to 5 years...
until they're sent out.
As they move around in a spacious place,
unlike other eels, they're chewier...
and less bitter.
(The eels are packed with energy!)
Please enjoy eels!
(Gwangyang, Wild eels)
Catching them with your bare hands is impossible.
- No way.
- I'm scared.
- You can't.
- I can't do it.
- I...
- Eels don't bite, do they?
- They don't. I asked too.
- No?
- They don't, even with their teeth?
- No.
Do we really catch them with our hands?
(They walk with heavy hearts.)
- Listen. Just fish...
- Aren't they gross?
I don't know. Fish? I'm scared to touch them with bare hands.
- Right?
- You're so cute.
- Why are you so cute?
- What?
Isn't it scary, Sun Young?
(Seeing Tough Girl Yoon Seo scared is rare.)
- The eels are all gathered here.
- Oh, my gosh.
Seriously, I...
(I'm scared of eels!)
Gosh, look at them.
- What do we do? Tell us quickly.
- Don't they grow here?
- I'm scared.
- How?
Today's labor is Gwangyang wild eel, a summer staple known...
for its restorative qualities, raised in pristine red clay soil.
- Wild?
- Wild.
- So those are wild eels.
- What does that mean?
Inside this pond, where you'll be working,
are around 4,000 eels.
- In here?
- In that pond?
Please catch...
all 4,000 eels.
- All of them?
- Catch all 4,000 eels?
- How can we catch all 4,000?
- No way.
- You want us to catch all 4,000?
- We each have to catch 1,000.
- That's impossible.
- At least 800 each.
- No one can catch 4,000.
- Oh, my.
- Hi.
We made a wild fish farm...
in the pine forest...
and are raising wild eels.
- You see the size of the eels?
- Yes.
The eels are huge and healthy.
As each eel...
- must be handled gently, - Okay.
Wear gloves...
- and catch one eel at a time.
- Okay.
(So we are using our hands to catch them.)
- The eel's body produces mucus.
- Right.
So you can't catch them with bare hands.
- I see.
(Eels' bodies are covered with slimy mucus.)
(Even with gloves on when catching eels, )
(they constantly escape.)
(Let go of me, human!)
Change your gloves often,
and together,
- We have to change our gloves.
- we'll put them in the buckets.
The gloves...
become all slimy from the mucus, right?
- Make sure to take a lot.
- Is that why?
- They slide out.
- Correct.
You have to constantly change them.
(She already has goosebumps.)
(Two, catching is done barefoot.)
Do we wear socks inside?
(Also barefoot?)
We work barefoot.
- Barefoot?
- Sorry?
Only when you go in barefoot...
can you feel the eels inside the mud.
(Why do we have to feel them?)
You have to catch the eels...
that are buried under the mud.
(You must catch the eels buried under the mud.)
(Using the sensation of their bare feet, )
(they have to track down the eels hiding in the mud.)
(Yes, with bare hands and barefoot.)
(Sighing)
- Take as many...
- Thank you.
- gloves as possible.
- Take a lot.
Take as many as you can.
(If you can't avoid it, )
(enjoy it!)
We're done if we catch all 4,000 within 30 minutes, right?
We just need to catch them all, right?
I even gave birth. This is easy peasy!
(Her socks are off.)
- Do we go down from here?
- Yes.
Carefully back your way down.
I'll catch the bucket...
- Okay.
- if you throw it down.
(You Seok is in the lead.)
(Muddy)
(Groaning)
Let's go.
(Entering the eel field with teamwork)
(Just you wait, eels!)
My feet hurt.
Slowly.
(Here we come!)
(Laughing)
Goodness gracious.
The feeling itself is...
(The mud)
It's the mud.
(Laughing)
(Struggling)
(Screaming)
(Yoon Seo is taken aback the minute she steps on the mud.)
This feeling is just too weird.
(Whimpering)
(Will the two be okay?)
Do you see the eels making their way out?
- Over there?
- Where are they going?
The eels are making their way out through that hole.
(Upper pond)
(A stepped fish farm)
(Lower pond)
(Digging into the feed)
(Once the upper pond eels have grown enough, )
(the water stopper opens.)
(It drains...)
(the water out.)
The eels follow the water.
(Following their instinct to seek out water, )
(the eels gather in the puddle.)
(The journey begins.)
The eels will follow the water...
as it's being drained.
(The eels will travel down to the lower pond.)
(Eels)
(Save us!)
(What awaits the eels in the lower pond is)
In the lower pond, the escaped eels...
are collected in an installed fish holder.
Do we work in the lower pond after we're done here?
Yes.
(Scooping them out is also part of today's job.)
(But...)
(there are eels casually swimming around...)
(and even escaping the waterway.)
They're unruly teenagers.
(Many eels are unruly.)
Catch the eel,
- put it in the bucket, - Okay.
- and empty it into the blue bucket.
- Okay.
(Method 1: Put the captured eels into the bucket...)
(and pour them into the water-filled bucket.)
Or you could drive the eels...
toward the waterhole and catch them.
(Method 2: Drive the eels to the hole.)
We simply have to drive the eels...
- to that hole.
- Correct.
There's no need to catch them.
- We can just drive them there.
- Yes.
But eels far away...
- are hard to drive.
- Right.
Catch the eels where there is no water first.
(Catch the eels that are outside the water first.)
- We have to catch eels like those.
- Catch ones...
- Correct.
- like these, right?
Catch ones like these, right?
(Guys that are outside the water)
- They're alive, right?
- Yes.
(Are you alive?)
(Thrashing)
(Of course, it's alive.)
You must catch them in one go.
(Tapping)
(Snatching it up in one swift move)
Oh, gosh.
It feels weird.
(Sliding out)
My gosh, you're strong.
Don't leave the bucket too far away.
(Groaning)
(Escaping)
How will we catch 4,000 like this?
Oh, my. They're escaping, just like snakes.
Oh, dear.
(Hi, Yoon Seo.)
I'm really scared.
Hold on. A calm one first.
(Calm versus Going wild)
Oh, no.
This is tough.
(A scream worthy of a yodel)
What do I do? I can't catch any.
(Saenggang is scared of eels despite catching ghosts.)
Help me.
(While Yoon Seo is begging for help)
They're like snakes.
We're supposed to catch these eels, right?
(How's Sun Young doing?)
Like so.
This guy is buried in the mud.
(Grabbing)
Let's go. Go in.
No, give me a second.
I don't know how hard I can grip it.
(Digging in)
How hard can I grab the eels?
You can just make a quick grab.
(Is that so?)
Hey, go in.
(Subduing the eels easily)
We must quickly catch the eels outside the water.
Let's go. Oh, my!
(Laughing)
(The eel You Seok lost)
Okay, come in here.
(Screaming)
Come in here.
(Trying to steal it all naturally)
Just look at how strong they are. Hold on.
(Simply bright)
(Meanwhile, You Seok is...)
- The eels are slippery.
- They slip out.
Hey, dude.
Even the captured ones escape.
An eel like that is super strong. Look.
- It's strong.
- Come here, Sun Young.
The eel digs in.
- Goodness.
- Go in. We did it.
(She's excited.)
(Jung Ah is also struggling to catch the eels.)
(Even if you caught one, )
(don't let your guard down.)
Even the captured ones escape.
No. Stop.
(Thrashing)
Gosh, no. Don't escape.
(Catching and losing on repeat)
They're slippery.
(Slipping in)
Where are you going?
The eels are hard to catch as is.
(Hide-and-seek begins.)
(Slipping out)
(Slipping out again)
They're all escaping.
It's moving towards my feet.
Come here. No, come here.
(An army of advancing eels)
(Meanwhile, Jin Hee was struggling in the game.)
(He spotted an army of eels.)
(Trying to scoop them into the bucket)
All of them escaped. This won't do.
- No, all of them escape.
- Right?
(Inhaling)
I can't.
(How should I catch them?)
Goodness.
(Keeping a sharp eye on them)
(Quickly snatching and tossing them into the basket)
Oh, my. Oh, dear.
(His strategy is to minimize the time they spend in his hands.)
(Snatching them up without hesitation)
(The eel hunter)
- You're good at it, Jin Hee.
- What?
You're good.
They're super slippery.
(Sweeping up every eel in sight)
You're amazing, Jin Hee.
I simply want to go home soon.
I'd better change my gloves.
(Let's get this over with quickly, okay?)
(Serious Jin Hee)
(Jin Hee has gotten the hang of it.)
(Slipping out)
(Although he loses them all.)
Oh, my.
(A mess)
(There's still one eel left.)
(While Jin Hee is working twice as much as the others)
Where are you going?
- Let's catch that one.
- Gosh.
(You Seok and Yoon Seo have teamed up.)
These are a bunch of unruly teenagers. Hey.
Who do you think you are?
(I have You Seok with me.)
- Come here. I've got eyes on you.
- You can't go up from there.
(Starting now, )
(it's time to teach you a lesson.)
There's no water over there.
(The targets: Unruly eels muddying the waters)
Many eels here have gone astray.
- Hey. Where are you going?
- Go ahead, make a fuss.
- It's gone in here.
- Oh, gosh.
Here.
You...
These unruly teenagers.
Accept it. Accept your fate.
Look at how far you're going.
Where are you going? Where are you going in such a rush?
Do you have a long way to go?
We're settling this today.
Let's see who wins.
Are you hiding under there?
But you're going to slither out, no?
(Tenacious Supervisor You Seok)
You little...
Oh, my.
Stay still, will you?
In you go!
- Go in! No!
- Oh, my.
No!
Come here.
(Hiding in the mud is no use.)
Look at this huge one. Look. It's huge.
It's the size of my forearm.
It's twice the size of the other one.
(The ringleader of the unruly eels has been taught a lesson.)
Goodness. Look at that one. What's with it?
Look at this one. It's the ringleader!
Look at it. We'd better eat it.
Even its fin looks different.
(To escape from Madam Wasp, )
(it's heading upstream?)
- Look at that guy.
- The fin.
It moved from here to there.
Stop them from going up.
- It's moving up.
- It already went all the way there.
(The eel leader is powering its way upstream.)
It's going the other way now!
Some eels go upstream.
(Against the flowing water)
(Swimming upstream)
(Are the eels)
This one's moving upstream really well.
Oh, my.
(Unbelievable vitality)
- Eels like this one.
- The eels follow the water.
As the water level drops,
the eels follow the waterway upstream.
(As the water recedes, the eels follow the waterway.)
These eels are full of energy.
No wonder they're eels.
It's my first time seeing live eels, and they're no joke.
(About to push through the water hose)
The eels are in a traffic accident.
(A traffic accident between eels going downstream and upstream)
Go this way.
Let's make them a path.
(Creating a waterway)
Don't swim this way. Go that way.
Hey.
Swim down.
(Persuading them gently)
That's upstream. Dude.
Hey, dude.
(Gave it a lesson)
Come here. Come in here.
Yes, that's it. Good.
(Surrendering)
(Their bodies are covered in mud.)
(But they work towards 4,000 eels!)
Go inside.
(Sighing)
Where do you think you're going?
- My back hurts.
- That's it.
Yes, this way.
(Splattering)
The mud is going into my eyes.
Hey, I'm going to...
Gosh! Oh, no. It's so strong.
(Catching them one by one is painful.)
Goodness. Hey!
Hey! Catching it is impossible.
(The eels are as energetic as ever.)
I'm exhausted. But it's not my body.
My mind is exhausted. What do I do? Hold on.
Come on.
(Except for this excited lady)
(They've mostly cleared out the areas farther from the waterway.)
(Thinking)
We don't have to catch the eels following...
- the waterway, right?
- Correct.
Herd them towards the water.
- That's a strategy.
- Right?
Let's herd them to the water...
- and catch them on the other side.
- Okay.
Herd them to that side.
(Herding the eels to the waterway)
- Herd them.
- Let's go.
Do I push them into the waterway?
Like this?
Go.
Go down. Let's go.
(Instead of catching the eels)
Go. Downwards, not upwards.
(They herd the eels toward the water.)
Leave the ones going downstream.
(Herding the eels full on)
- That way.
- Go.
Go.
(Pushing them)
Go. No.
(Pushing them on all fours)
That way. Yes.
- Go that way.
- Go.
- You little...
No, it's not that way.
That's upstream, dude.
Go that way.
I'm tired.
(Completely battered and worn out)
Let's go.
I feel like a sheepdog.
(As a result of herding the eels)
Where are you going?
Go.
(Half water, half eels)
(Let's pour the eels that were inside the blue bucket.)
Do we push the eels inside?
- Do we push them in?
- Yes.
Can you come over here and help us push...
- the eels into the hole?
- Okay.
(It's time to push the eels into the hole.)
It's overcrowded.
(It's overcrowded!)
- Like this? Do I push like this?
- Yes, towards the hole.
Go in.
(They start to direct traffic.)
(With his body all covered in mud, )
(Jin Hee guides the eels to the hole.)
This is no easy job. My back is killing me.
(Out of energy)
Wait. It went into my eye.
(Screaming)
The eel took my eye.
(Often falling victim to the eels' mud attacks)
(Even the workaholic Captain Yum)
(She's clearly showing signs of exhaustion.)
(Meanwhile, Sun Young is...)
Unbelievable.
(Screaming)
(She starts pushing through with sheer grit.)
Here.
Come this way.
Oh, my.
(Groaning)
(Sun Young has even gone down on her knees.)
Come here.
(Rounding up the eels)
Sun Young is...
(A horror movie from the eels' perspective)
They're gone now.
(She's become an eel herself.)
(Sweeping the mud)
Here. Go.
I'm beat.
I can't feel a thing now, even if you crawl under my feet.
Not anymore.
I don't care what you do.
Even my underwear is wet.
Really.
- Let's go.
- There are tons here.
- I see.
- I'll help.
Go.
(The siblings muster up some strength.)
These little...
Go.
Go that way.
No. Go.
You little... Go!
(Herding the eels with gibberish)
(You Seok arrests the eels that have run away from home without a break.)
Come here.
You too.
(After battling with 4,000 eels)
There aren't that many left now.
In you go.
(10 minutes ago)
This way. That's it.
(Now)
Someone has to keep pushing them down.
(Guiding the motionless eels down by hand)
We're almost done.
(We're almost done!)
(They're completely tattered.)
(She turned into this in just an hour.)
(So did this man.)
(Ji Jin Hee, covered in mud)
- Stay here and wrap this up.
- Okay.
(While Jung Ah is forcing the eels into the hole...)
They shouldn't be out here too long. They need to be in the water.
There's another one here.
(Shivering with fear)
Here we go.
She said we had to stomp on the mud...
to find the eels, right?
Let's find them.
Oh, here it is.
I found one. All right.
(I won't miss a single eel!)
There you are.
Impressive. You're good at this.
Jin Hee is so good at this.
(The eel hunter really has this down.)
I think I learned the ropes.
You don't want to go, do you? But there's nothing you can do.
(Meanwhile, here's another eel hunter.)
I really want to catch just one... I want to catch a really big one...
that's hiding somewhere here.
Catching eels gives me that same thrill as fishing.
(In search of a dopamine rush, she looks for an eel.)
My gosh. They're so good at hiding.
(Scouring the mud for a while...)
Oh, I found one!
Nice. I got you, you brat.
- I got you, you brat.
- "You brat."
(Her dopamine level is skyrocketing.)
I caught this one.
It's a really big one.
So this is how you catch an eel.
(An eel fanatic is born.)
You should go this way. Go this way.
(All the eels have gone down to the lower pond.)
Let's head over to the other pond and start scooping them up.
Just one more eel.
(The eel fanatic still wants to catch more eels.)
Oh, I found one. Hey, you brat.
- Hold on.
- I can...
- It's so strong.
- I'm good at this. I can catch it.
- Grab it hard. Like this.
- Gosh, it's escaping.
- Nice.
- Like this! Let's go!
- Let's go.
(They're insanely confident and pumped up.)
Sun Young always has amazing chemistry...
- with the guests.
- Let's go!
I'm really good at catching eels, right?
(Her skills at holding down eels backs up her confidence.)
(Giggling)
Go on in. Oh, my. Look at this one.
Hey, I told you to go in.
Oh, yes.
- Nice. High five.
- Nice.
- Jin Hee.
- Great job.
(The eel fanatic and the eel hunter have brilliant teamwork.)
I think we're done here.
I counted the eels. We caught 4,282 eels.
- I counted them too.
- You did?
- Yes, we caught 4,280.
- How many were they?
- Oh, I guess I counted two more.
- I think we did a flawless job.
- Okay. That's accurate.
- Yes.
(He looks around more until the very end.)
Okay. There's none.
- We actually caught 4,000 eels.
- That's amazing.
(The work in the upper pond is done with a total of 4,282 eels.)
- Catching eels is quite thrilling.
- Really?
- You're just incredible.
- I can grab it in a single try.
- I wanted...
- You beat them.
Yes. I wanted to catch just one more.
I came out reluctantly.
You're in trouble. You're a total mess.
I don't care, Jung Ah. You just have to grab it hard.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Thank you.
(I gave it my all.)
It's no joke.
Since eels are so strong, it takes so much out of you.
- The work took a toll on my eyes.
- Me too. Gosh, seriously.
I feel like I have something in my eyes.
(The younger members got stuff in their eyes while working.)
I guess it's easier for stuff to get in your eyes since they're so big.
I don't easily get stuff in my eyes since they're small.
(Kidding)
That's not true. Your eyes are very big.
They're small. That's why I can't see things clearly.
- Pardon me?
- You can see a lot with big eyes.
With big eyes, you can see a lot. With small eyes, you can't.
(Ji Jin Hee with clear vision, Ji Jin Hee with blurry vision)
(Jin Hee is like an uncle acting cute in front of his niblings.)
By the way, you did such a great job.
Me? I figured out the trick.
I think we'll work in here, scooping the eels up with a net.
They came down from up there, right?
They're all in that green net.
They all slid through the pipe and straight into the fish holder.
(Yoon Seo figured something out after long observation.)
The water there is waist-deep.
- I have no extra underwear.
- I think we'll take this off...
I brought many pairs.
Mine won't work for you?
I just don't know.
Roh Yoon Seo and Yum Jung Ah are out.
Why? Because you have no extra underwear?
(He seems serious.)
You were supposed to pack extra pairs of underwear.
You must've known this could happen. Then why did you not bring any?
I didn't know we'd do this kind of work.
I had no idea.
You didn't know it would be like this?
But at least, you sweat because it's summer.
(It's summer. I don't understand.)
We were not told we'd get soaked all the way to our underwear.
They told us to pack clean clothes, but not underwear.
You're not little kids. Do they need to spell everything out for you?
Do you keep them in your pocket? Are they in your car? Where are they?
- I mean...
- I packed a lot in my bag.
I pack more than two pairs per day, just in case.
You're always so well-prepared.
(The best senior actor)
They can't do it because they don't have extra underwear...
It's not like that.
It seems that not many can go in it.
- That's good. Let's go.
- Do you want this?
(Sun Young, You Seok, and Jin Hee get ready to go in first.)
Hold on. If we go in there, we'll get soaked to our underwear.
My underwear is still clean.
Why is your underwear still clean?
I tried not to get wet that high up. I got wet only up to here...
Or did I not? Maybe I...
Wait. Let me check.
If I described the state of my underwear, it would be censored.
(The state of Sun Young's underwear is definitely not TV-appropriate.)
Why didn't they tell us to pack extra underwear?
I already complained about that many times.
Do they really need to tell you to pack basics like toothpaste?
Do you seriously need a notice to pack your toothbrush and stuff?
- You should've told us to pack it.
- You didn't tell us to bring...
Forget it. Here's what we're going to do from now on.
Let's pack extra underwear even if they don't tell us to.
It's our fault.
- Okay. Got it.
- Underwear...
(The underwear uprising ended as they figured out a solution.)
(Jin Hee, who was watching the situation...)
- Oh, I get it.
- Here's what we're going to do.
I get it now. So you don't have clean underwear here, right?
You have them at the place you're staying, right?
(The misunderstanding is finally cleared up after all this time.)
- Of course, Jin Hee.
- Of course, we have them there.
- We wouldn't wear it for 3 days...
- It's a 3-day shoot.
What do you take us for?
I thought, "Gosh, those stupid punks."
I couldn't understand why you didn't bring extra underwear.
We have them at the place where we're staying.
(Now, it's time to work!)
- What should we do?
- How does this work?
How is it done?
(Under the pond where they were catching eels just moments ago...)
We set up a fish holder in the lower pond,
and the escaped eels gather in it.
(The eels that the four siblings pushed into the hole...)
(slid down the pipe.)
(Swarming)
(Get into the fish holder where the eels gathered.)
In there, you will use a net.
(Scoop the eels out using a net.)
(Put the eels in the bucket.)
(And then, transfer them into the water tanks.)
I counted the eels. We caught 4,282 eels.
(With the 4,282 eels they caught, according to Jin Hee...)
(They can get up close and personal with the eels.)
The one in there scoop them out and pass them to you.
And then you pass them to the next person.
Who wants to go in there?
The one in there scoop them out and pass them to you.
And then you pass them to the next person.
Who wants to go in there?
Let's all take turns.
- Shall we take turns in order?
- Yes.
I'll go first.
(Sun Young, the human wasp, is the first to go!)
(She gets into the fish holder with Jin Hee's help.)
Oh, gosh. Hold on.
What I'm feeling at the bottom are eels, right?
- Yes.
- Right.
(Once she steps in, she can feel the eels wiggling against her legs.)
There are a lot of eels...
- around her legs.
- The eels we caught. Yes.
They must be wiggling against her legs right now.
- They must be wiggling like this.
- Like this.
She's so brave.
This is the hardest part.
This is the hardest part?
Yes. You have to scoop the eels out with that net.
(Each eel weighs 1kg on average.)
(About 4,000 eels they caught multiplied by 1kg equals...)
(About 4t!)
(They have to scoop out 4t of eels in total with a net!)
It must be really exhausting.
I'll give it a try.
(The eel fanatic learns how to use the net.)
(Going in)
(Step 1: Push the net as deep as possible.)
All the way to the wall? Because if we don't, they will escape?
(An eel fountain explodes.)
(Passing the net)
(It looks heavy at a glance.)
What?
(Shocked)
(The eels that were moved into the bucket...)
One, two, three.
(should be transferred straight into the water tanks!)
(They work in pairs so they don't lose the precious eels.)
(Delivering the eels to the waiting water tank)
(The first delivery is complete.)
Pushing it into the water like this...
(Now, they have to move about 4,267kg of eels.)
(The eel fanatic tries to use the net as she learned.)
(She pushes the net as deep as it goes.)
(Then she pushes it toward the wall.)
(After driving enough eels into the net, she lifts it up.)
Here we go.
(She can feel the eels' power through her hands.)
(Looks like she got a massive scoop of eels.)
(Lifting)
Hold there.
(Sun Young scooped out more eels than the eel farm owner.)
My goodness. She scooped out so many eels.
(Even the eel farm worker is surprised by the sheer volume.)
(I'm good at this, right?)
So, you don't catch the eels with your bare hands here.
Catching them with your bare hands is more fun.
(Sun Young is disappointed that she can't catch them barehanded.)
(So she scoops eels out.)
(She scoops out more eels.)
(Even when she's surrounded by a school of eels...)
Let's go! That's good!
(She shows no hesitation.)
(She doesn't mind getting soaked. She might just dive into the water.)
Okay.
(She keeps scooping eels to make up for not using her bare hands.)
(Run!)
That's what I'm talking about.
(She's a disaster for the eels.)
(Chuckling)
(You brats)
(Do not run away, eels.)
(You'll end up in my net anyway.)
Sun Young, you're so cool.
I could even take a bath in here.
(That's sheer madness.)
I want to catch them with my bare hands.
But I can't do that in here.
(They're simply amazed.)
I see a whole bunch of eels here.
(While Sun Young, the eel fanatic, is riding a crazy dopamine rush...)
We can do it faster if we do it in pairs, right?
- You mean, scooping them out?
- Yes, I'll help her...
scoop them out in the fish holder.
(Jin Hee decided to go into the water.)
(He starts scooping eels out!)
(Jin Hee pushes the net as if he were scraping the bottom.)
(Skillful)
(He got a massive scoop in one go.)
Oh, my. That's a lot.
Jin Hee, you're so good at this...
- He's good. He's strong too.
- Indeed.
- What would we do without him?
- Exactly.
(Seriously, what would they do without Jin Hee?)
(Everyone raves about Jin Hee, who's doing a great job.)
(Jin Hee, until you came...)
(I've never been caught.)
(Jin Hee, you have no idea...)
(that there's no one else who does better than you.)
(He's good at this.)
(Next to Jin Hee, who's working hard and quietly...)
(Laughing)
Oh, my. This is no joke. It's so satisfying.
- Here we go.
- Come on in, you brats.
All right. Here we go.
(The mad net duo)
How about we work as a team?
- Okay.
- Good.
Push it down into the water.
(They push their nets down into the water first!)
- Push it down. Two, three.
- One, two, three. Let's go.
(Jin Hee's plan is to drive the eels in the same direction!)
(Grunting)
(Their teamwork brought a great result.)
But when will we finish scooping out all these eels?
There are 4,000 eels in here.
- Yes. That's good.
- Oh, gosh.
(A replacement appears.)
Oh, my. This is amazing.
(While You Seok is amazed by the first-time sensation...)
See?
(Yoon Seo joins them.)
(Jin Hee is in charge of moving the eels.)
Be careful.
(Be careful, Jin Hee.)
(Passing the bucket)
- I was told to go this way.
- I'll show you how it's done.
- Let's drive them together.
- I learned how to do this.
- Push it down and step forward.
- Yes.
When it hits the wall,
(Drive them.)
- lift it up. Oh, gosh.
- Gosh.
(The younger members who are still energetic...)
It's so heavy.
(They drive the eels with their youthful energy.)
Gosh, it's so heavy.
(In the cool water, they enjoy the thrilling sensation.)
We won't need to go to the valley today.
- We're having all the fun in here.
- This basically is...
This basically is the valley.
(No!)
Calm down.
Please calm down. Can you...
You caught too many eels.
I think I caught too many.
(Yoon Seo got a massive scoop that's as big as herself.)
This won't be easy.
(The eels caught by Yoon Seo are too heavy for even two men to lift.)
Oh, my. It's a lot.
(The younger members, who are still energetic, are doing a great job.)
Sun Young is winking.
(Is this a wink?)
(It's an unusual wink, but it cheers me up.)
(Winking)
(The siblings muster up more energy.)
I caught too many.
(Even when a ton of eels are caught, she lifts them up easily.)
There are eels absolutely everywhere.
(Scoop out all the eels surrounding you.)
It's no joke, right?
I am the wild eel.
Let's go.
One, two, three. It's too heavy for you. Leave it.
(Current progress: 3,400kg scooped out of 4,282kg)
(Meanwhile, the eel farm owner is doing something.)
Oh, he's gathering the eels.
(Since there aren't many eels left, he's tightening the fish holder.)
There are still a lot of eels in here.
(They start scooping eels up again to wrap it up quickly.)
It's broken.
It's broken?
Let's throw this out.
My goodness.
(The pole of Jin Hee's net snapped.)
(Jin Hee just uses the net part to keep going!)
Let's go.
(Watching Jin Hee's amazing ability to get the job done, )
(everyone is simply impressed.)
(Thanks to the amazing work done by Jin Hee, the great worker...)
- It's finally close to an end.
- One, two...
It's closing in more and more.
(They must be almost done.)
(The fish holder has been tightened so much.)
Jin Hee, aren't you tired?
I'm tired, but this is fun.
It's fun, indeed, but...
When was the last time I worked this hard...
I think it's been 30 years since I last worked this hard.
Did you perhaps appear on a show...
like "Experience the Scene of Life?"
I didn't even go on "Experience the Scene of Life."
Oh, you didn't?
No, I thought it'd be too exhausting.
(Jin Hee refused to go on the show, thinking it'd be too exhausting.)
You Seok, you said you wanted to go to the valley.
(Shaking his head)
You don't need to go there?
Valley, my foot.
"Valley, my foot."
(That's so funny.)
We're actually almost done.
(Touched)
This is unbelievable.
I think this is the hardest work we've ever done on the show.
(Even though it's hard work...)
Be careful. They might escape.
Oh, that's good.
(Crowding around, they move the eels to the bucket.)
(Let's see.)
Done! There's none left, right?
- All right!
- There's none left!
(The work is done.)
I wish I could just lie down here.
Good job, guys. How many eels did we catch earlier?
- We caught 8,000 eels.
- I don't even know.
No, we caught 9,000 eels.
- I'm so...
- How many eels were there?
(They did a great job.)
- Great job, everyone.
- Great job.
- I can't believe we pulled it off.
- Exactly.
(After finishing the legendary eel catching work...)
(She's completely spaced out.)
Do you know what's happening to me?
This is what a dopamine addict ends up looking like.
You jump in thinking it'd be fun, and you end up like this.
You were indeed high on dopamine earlier.
This is why you shouldn't chase a dopamine rush too much.
(Too much dopamine is the shortcut to ruining your everyday life.)
Have some snacks.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you for your help.
- Don't mention it.
- Thank you.
- Oh, my.
- What are these?
Gwangyang is the green plum capital of Korea.
(The snack set of green plums, Gwangyang's specialty)
These are plum blossom bread, green plum cream cheese bread,
and green plum muffin.
And I made slushy for you...
with the green plum syrup that my mom made.
(I love it.)
It was really hot, wasn't it?
- Thanks.
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you. We'll enjoy it.
- Thank you.
It feels like we're on a battlefield.
(She agrees.)
It's as if we were refugees...
eating on the side of the road.
We're eating boiled eggs.
As if we were eating the food we carried in our bags.
(They start eating the snack, looking like refugees.)
(She drinks cool green plum syrup slushy first.)
- It's good.
- It's so delicious.
I love this green plum slushy.
(It feels even cooler and sweeter after the hard work.)
It's so cool.
Is this our lunch?
No, that's breakfast.
- What time is it now?
- What about lunch?
It's 9:17am now.
- It's only 9am now?
- Really?
It's 9am now?
(She can't believe it.)
We left at 5:30am.
Then what should we do now?
We should go back and take a nap.
- I have no idea.
- Seriously...
She keeps looking at me while speaking, but I have no idea.
(Sun Young's gaze bewildered Jin Hee.)
I wish I could tell her something, but I have nothing to say.
(I'm sorry.)
- Jin Hee, what do you want to do?
- What do you want to do?
- Is there something you want to do?
For example, we could go to the valley or go ziplining.
(Magnet Kang slyly recommends what he likes to do.)
(Seriously, he's unbelievable.)
I think he's suggesting...
- we should try one of those.
- What do you like to do?
What do you like to do?
The valley...
(He stubbornly mentions the valley.)
He's hooked.
- No. It's not that.
- It's not that I'm hooked.
He only mentions whatever he wants to do.
(Magnet Kang's Victim 1)
Ziplining... Wait.
Can only one of us go ziplining?
- We can use only 1 of the 2 lines.
- Or the House...
- The House of Choi Champan!
(Oh, right. That was it.)
It's not Kim Cheom Ji's house. It's the House of Choi Champan.
- Is that a Chinese restaurant?
- No.
(What's this house about?)
(His question makes everyone crack up.)
I want jjamppong.
(Why are you guys laughing? I want jjamppong.)
(His double combo catches him off guard.)
I'm going to cry.
(He's so funny that he's going to make me cry.)
I'm crying here.
Oh, my back.
(But the jokester is calm.)
I'm crying here.
I'm so exhausted that I can't stop laughing.
(Their fun snack time is over.)
Great job catching wild eels today.
I'll give you the shipping fee.
(It's time to collect the shipping fee.)
What is it?
(Humming to bring up the excitement level)
We're expecting a big payment.
(He looks majestic like a triumphal general.)
Let's see. How much did we get?
One, two, three, four...
nine, ten.
That's good. We got 150 dollars. That's enough.
Thank you.
- Grill these at home. Enjoy.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
She's such a cool daughter.
- Let's definitely grill this.
- It's all cleaned and prepared.
- That's a relief.
- Awesome.
(Cleaned and prepared eels for them to eat right away)
- Thank you.
- This is...
Wild eels are so precious.
- They farmed these for five years.
- Yes.
I love eels.
- Me too. I love them too.
- Yes.
- Let's enjoy them today.
- I like eels too.
(Let's enjoy them today.)
(The wild eels that are caught by the siblings...)
(are put in an indoor aquarium for a week...)
(to get rid of the muddy smell.)
(After they're cleaned and prepared...)
(Fresh food, handle with care)
(they're shipped off all across the country.)
That was tough, but it was definitely rewarding.
- Right?
- Yes.
So that's how we started our morning.
- Gosh, it's only 10am now.
- It's going to be a long day.
Exactly.
- My legs don't feel like mine.
- We're falling behind.
These are my legs, right?
- I want to catch up.
- Right?
- This was the hardest one yet.
- Right? It was the hardest.
- It's the hardest labor so far.
- Okay.
But we still have to do it...
- for the viewers.
- She's so funny.
For the viewers,
- we must do it. What else?
- We must do it. What else?
(We must catch eels for the viewers.)
I got a dopamine rush...
- This was the look on your face.
- from the eels.
- It was this.
- "Eels!"
"I'm having so much fun."
It was fun.
(The oldest sibling quickly gets to the car.)
- Are you sure you can drive?
- Of course.
- Do you have anything to put away?
- What? No.
(She must be tired too, )
(but she volunteers to handle the long drive back.)
- Switch places with me.
- Gosh, I'm good here.
Just get comfy and get some sleep now.
Let's take a nap, You Seok.
- Sun Young.
- Yes.
(Thanks to her, they can take a nap anytime.)
- Jin Hee, if I miss the GPS, - Okay. I'll keep an eye on it.
- let me know which way to go.
- Okay.
Are you going to take a nap?
The direct distance isn't far,
but we had to go around. That's why.
(She starts driving as she relies on Jin Hee.)
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- Is it a shorter way back?
- It takes about an hour.
It takes 56 minutes. The direct distance is short.
But we have to go around. We have no choice.
I see.
(It's a bumpy ride because the road isn't paved.)
Go straight.
Okay.
(The three in the back are enjoying the bumpy ride.)
- Jung Ah.
- It's off-roading.
(Shaky)
Go straight and turn left when you see the main road.
- Make a left turn here.
- We have to turn left, right?
Yes, turn left.
(Thanks to him, she smoothly enters the main road.)
Go straight now.
Follow this road and go straight.
Turn left when you see another road.
You have such a great voice.
Right. You sound like the GPS.
(His voice is as smooth as that of GPS.)
You have a cool voice.
(Losing energy at the sudden burst of attention on him)
(Sorrowful eyes)
- He's so cool.
- Were we hasty in approaching you?
- Yes. A bit.
- Should we...
- take a step back?
- If you feel it's too soon,
- A bit. Okay.
- you should call out a color.
If you think it's too soon,
- you can say, "yellow."
- Yellow.
- "Green" is for when you feel okay.
- Okay.
If you can't take it, you cay say "red."
- Like the traffic light.
(The traffic light is on for Shy Jin Hee.)
- Red - Jin Hee
Could you sing us a song?
- That's... Yellow.
- Red?
No. It's red.
He said "red."
- Red - He said it.
It's red.
- We got 1 red and 1 yellow.
- He's so nice.
- He gave us a yellow card.
- I have a question.
Is it possible to get kicked out?
Kick someone out? Well, that's...
You'd be in trouble if you get kicked out here.
Not here.
There should be a rule that a certain number of yellow...
and red cards would result in being kicked out.
Then I probably got kicked out a long time ago.
- Then...
- That's so cute.
- we can't talk for a few hours.
- She already got kicked out.
She got kicked out a long time ago.
(There's no way.)
Didn't you major in Philosophy?
- Yes.
- I envy you.
- I love...
- How did you know?
- Well, everyone knows that.
- How...
What? I didn't know that.
- How did you know that?
- You majored in Art, right?
(He already knows personal information about them?)
Did you look us up before coming here?
Of course, I did.
- You graduated from K-Arts.
- Really?
That's so touching.
He looked all of us up.
(Touched)
- Didn't you major in Visual Design?
- Earlier...
- Yes, I did.
- you were...
- Did you look it up?
- I already knew that.
- You did?
- I've known it for some time.
- Right. I read it somewhere too.
- I see.
- You also majored in Art.
- Visual Design.
- Really?
- He studied Visual Design.
After studying Visual Design,
I got into acting.
- Right.
- So I checked you out.
We're kind of similar.
- He has a big heart.
- Yes.
- Yellow.
Gosh, when will we get green?
- Are you going to sleep?
- No.
- You Seok.
- I'm listening.
- Get him to say green.
- We never got green.
- I'm thinking about what to do.
How can we get green?
Green.
(Green?)
(Knocked out)
You can lean on me.
(Massaging)
This part of my shoulder is bony.
- If you lean on me here...
- No.
- He must be exhausted.
- They're getting knocked out.
(He massages his wrist to ease the fatigue.)
- This is nice.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- It's beautiful.
- It's such a beautiful village.
- Look.
- Right.
Look on your right. Isn't it beautiful?
- We're at the foot of Mount Jiri.
- Yes.
- Right. That's a cool mountain.
- Hwagae Market.
That's the entrance to Hwagae Market.
(Hwagae Market)
Seomjin River.
- That's Seomjin River?
- Seomjin River.
We were at Seomjin River yesterday.
- We harvested marsh clams there.
- Marsh clams.
Green tea fields look beautiful.
Is that our future for tomorrow?
What?
- They must be green tea fields.
- I bet.
- Just...
- They're all near our place.
- Yes. They're all green tea fields.
- I think...
(As they travel on the road, admiring the mountain view...)
What an amazing view.
Hey, shouldn't we eat something?
- You're peckish, right?
- We... Right?
How about having some ramyeon when we arrive? We can crack eggs.
That sounds so good.
All right. It's time to show him our house.
- Yes.
- Gosh.
Thank you for driving us.
Sure.
- Thank you for driving us.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Thank you so much for driving us.
No. I'm okay. I have good core muscles.
It looked like you had none.
When you fell earlier, you had no core.
- Jin Hee, go ahead.
- You can take the lead.
- There's a huge rock.
- I see a rock.
- Isn't it fascinating?
- This is amazing.
It reminds me of a house in "My Neighbor Totoro."
- Right?
- There's a rock.
- There are trees too.
- It's a great house.
- Yes, I can see that.
- It's nice and peaceful.
This place looks great.
(The more he looks around, the more beautiful he finds it.)
(As the house is right up his alley, )
(he takes a step back and admires it.)
(Something in the house catches his eyes.)
- Yes, that's it.
- Please take a look.
- That's what we told you about.
- Take a look at that.
- Please take a look.
- It's what we told you about.
It's great.
That's our family photo.
(Stopping)
(Giggling)
- My gosh.
- Look at their eyes.
- That crazy look in their eyes.
- Right.
Don't we look funny?
He looks funny in the picture. You look hilarious.
- Gosh, you've got an amazing house.
- Jin Hee. Let us...
- We'll give you the tour.
- Right?
Come here. This is your room.
(Amazed)
This looks so cute.
See? He likes stuff like that.
- What?
- As soon as he saw it...
(Surprised)
- What a cute attic.
- It is, right?
Yes.
- Gosh, this place is so cute.
- It's cute.
- How did they find...
- Right?
Ramyeon sounds so good. I haven't had ramyeon in a while.
Let's cook it quickly.
I don't know why I'm so hungry.
- Earlier today...
- Our labor today was draining.
- We had to use a lot of energy.
- Yes.
I haven't had ramyeon in ages. I'm serious.
Really? I've been craving ramyeon lately too.
It's been so long since I had it because I've been on a diet.
Oh, no.
Like the music video, "Ditto."
(The younger siblings film a video of their ramyeon dance.)
(Chili pepper and green onion)
Jin Hee. Let's eat...
- only a bit of rice for dinner.
- Yes.
- Let's have a clean meal with eels.
- That's right.
Sounds good.
- The ladle...
- We need to lift the noodles.
(He solemnly lifts the noodles.)
(Sharp)
This way, the noodles get firm and chewy.
(This way, the noodles get firm and chewy.)
This is perfect.
(The firm and chewy noodles are ready with the master's touch.)
Is it ready?
If you want your noodles firm, have it now.
Here are the mixed noodles.
No way.
- We have kkakdugi in the fridge.
- Kkakdugi.
- Awesome.
- Kkakdugi looks so good.
- Gosh.
- Enjoy.
- Dig in.
- Thank you for the food.
(They whip up ramyeon for a light meal.)
(She tastes the broth first.)
It hits the spot.
(Jin Hee blows on the noodles...)
(and has a big bite.)
(Humming)
- Yes.
- It's so good after hard labor.
- Seriously.
- Yes.
(He eats kkakdugi after a bite of the ramyeon.)
It's so good.
(Their body is covered in mud.)
(But that's why it's tastier.)
It's good.
Because we added the spicy chili peppers...
It's so good.
The spicy flavor is waking up all my senses.
(It's so spicy that it wakes up their senses.)
It's a bit spicy.
(But that spicy heat keeps them coming back for more.)
- It's good.
- It's so good.
(Salivating)
- Right.
- Ramyeon...
- It's crazy.
- It's delicious.
- It's so hot.
- Gosh, the broth...
(They sit around and share ramyeon together.)
- It's good.
- What's good?
The kimchi.
- It's fermented, right?
- It's already fermented.
(The siblings put their rough morning behind them.)
I feel alive again.
My gosh, we're eating a lot.
Yes, we are.
(Enjoying a peaceful moment on a full stomach)
My goodness. It feels so peaceful.
I might get super drowsy after a shower.
You rarely take a shower.
Jin Hee, why do you keep...
(Laughing)
- It's cool here.
- Where should we go later?
I'd love to visit both places.
- Okay.
- The traditional pub and valley?
I thought we were going to the traditional pub.
(When Magnet Kang takes over...)
- The traditional pub...
- Let's not go to the valley.
- Like a drinking spot, right?
- Seriously.
- I can't go to the valley.
- Yes.
(Actually, since last night...)
What are we going to do tomorrow afternoon?
No. Let's do nothing.
(The oldest sibling tried to stop him.)
I'll go by myself.
I'll go to the valley and the House of Choi Chumpan.
The House of...
(Stuttering)
(He looked up more places to visit again.)
Is that a famous tourist spot?
- Of course.
- Really?
- The House of Choi Champan?
- I'll go and have fun alone.
(I'll go even if it's just me.)
- Let's go to that famous house.
- Let's go to the valley...
and eat some watermelon.
I can't go in the water.
- Don't then.
- Just dip your legs in.
I can't dip my body in the water again.
Just your ankles then.
Let's go and have some watermelon.
(Magnet Kang won't back down easily as expected.)
You know what I think? He's going to the valley today.
It's going to be cold there.
- It won't be.
- It'll be cool there.
- No, be objective.
- Listen.
The weather has been cool.
Aren't you sleepy now that we ate?
Yes. Let's take a nap for an hour.
Time for a nap.
(They'll take a nap since they started their day early.)
Let's take a nap, Yoon Seo.
- Okay.
- Yoon Seo.
Yoon Seo.
(She naturally turns around.)
Sun Young. I feel alive again.
(They fall asleep, hugging each other.)
(You Seok is squirming to sleep outside the room.)
(This guy has no one or no blanket to hug.)
(I'll hug myself.)
(Jin Hee falls asleep just like that.)
(Jin Hee smoothly wakes up.)
(It seems he's playing with his favorite fan.)
- Hello?
- Hey.
What are you doing?
(He's calling his wife in his spare time.)
I'm taking a break.
We caught eels today.
My gosh. We went into the mud.
(He quietly brags about his experience.)
We caught over 4,000 eels.
- You'll have eels today then.
- Probably.
The local eels are amazing.
(Jin Hee keeps on boasting about the eels.)
Buy some.
I can't buy the eels here.
I think we can buy from an online platform.
(The well-prepared husband already found out everything.)
It's a very nice village too.
It's around the military base where I served.
(Jin Hee continues to shine as a sweet husband...)
It's right at the foot of Mount Jiri.
(as he talks to his wife.)
Of course.
Yes.
You Seok, you couldn't sleep?
(The siblings start to wake up one at a time.)
(Jin Hee comes out and exchanges greetings.)
- Did you get some sleep?
- I passed out.
- That's great.
- Did you sleep well?
That's good. You feel a little refreshed, right?
- Yes.
- Taking a nap for an hour...
The weather is amazing.
(He looks out, still half asleep.)
(The weather?)
Hey. We need to apply a lot of sunscreen. Jin Hee.
(When the siblings were enjoying their sweet nap...)
Gosh, the weather looks amazing.
- The sun is high at noon.
- Right.
- Gosh, how can it be this sunny?
- Right?
(Sunny without a single patch of shade)
(Given the weather...)
We could stay under the tree shade at the valley. So we might be okay.
- I won't go in the water.
- But should I still pack it?
- I'm serious. I'm not going in.
Come on. I know you'll go in. Don't say that.
- I won't.
- I'll only dip my feet in.
- Let's go to that famous house.
- The House of Choi Champan?
(Since we're in Hadong, let's go to that house.)
(And this guy won't miss this chance.)
We should go. There's a famous tourist spot in Hadong.
Let's go to Mr. Choi's house.
It's the House of Choi Champan.
It's a famous spot in Hadong.
We ought to visit the most famous spot in Hadong.
(It looks like we have to go now.)
(She quietly opens the fridge.)
Jin Hee, I can't carry the watermelon.
Okay. I got it. All right.
Is this a bomb? What's up with the color?
(He brings out the watermelon.)
It looks like a watermelon.
Gosh, it's the bomb I've only seen in anime.
My gosh, this looks good.
I bet it's tasty.
My gosh. This is a watermelon?
(Excited You Seok quickly puts on his swimsuit.)
(They're the best.)
- I stopped drawing on my eyebrows.
- You should finish then.
(Yoon Seo is ready for the valley.)
(Sun Young is going to draw on her eyebrows.)
- This too.
- Be careful with the knife.
I packed it.
- I wrapped it with a towel.
- I... Okay.
Are we going?
- Let's go.
Bye.
Only we're wearing swimsuits.
Did you guys recover a bit?
- Of course.
- Taking a nap helped.
I was catching eels in my dream.
Really?
You too?
(Staring)
- You're lying, right?
- No.
I meant to say that our labor this morning felt like a dream.
I...
- If we were to catch them now, - Jung Ah.
- I think I'd be better at it.
- I'm just disappointed...
I was too scared of them at first.
(Bummed out)
It would've been really tough if we didn't have...
- Right.
- Jin Hee today.
- We couldn't have finished.
- There was no way we could do it.
(Right. We couldn't have finished.)
(There was no way we could do it.)
- Without him...
- We could do it because we had him.
- Seriously.
- Yes.
- He was amazing.
- He was so helpful.
Right.
Are you going to stay with us until tomorrow evening?
(Laughing)
Jin Hee.
He got here the earliest, but he's leaving the latest.
I'll go home.
No. You can't leave us.
When will you go and harvest the green tea leaves?
But you're not even sure. Right?
- We're not sure yet.
- We don't know that either.
- It's just our speculation.
- We don't know what will happen.
- Oh, right.
- Yes.
But I need to leave before that.
(I don't know when you'll start, but I need to leave before that.)
I think I have to drive somewhere tomorrow.
- This work thing just popped up.
- No. Wait.
I also have a table read.
You Seok has a shoot in the morning.
But this is your show.
This is your work. You need to work.
This is all of our work.
- Jin Hee.
- Right, this is your work.
(Their main job is acting.)
I came here without any pressure.
I'm under so much pressure now.
- He's under so much pressure.
- I'm under so much pressure.
- He's...
- He came without any pressure.
- You can't leave.
- I see. To go and make it?
(The bottom line is you can't leave.)
After listening to you guys, I should leave tomorrow.
No. Someone has to stay and help.
Someone has to help.
(They cross over the Seomjin River...)
(where they harvested marsh clams yesterday.)
- Gosh, what a view.
- Look at the rocks.
(Amazed)
- How...
- It's so picturesque.
This is amazing.
(A picturesque view unfolds before their eyes.)
I wonder what kind of amazing valley is waiting for us.
(What kind of amazing valley awaits us?)
Gosh, we must be getting close.
(They arrive at the valley as they admire the view.)
Gosh, it's downhill.
(They enter a small side road.)
Is that a dead end?
What's going on?
(The road looks a bit creepy.)
- Thank you for driving us.
- Thank you.
My gosh. Let's get out of the car.
(They've arrived.)
(They came to the valley, recommended by the elders.)
- My gosh.
- Come on out.
(No matter how hard they look, they can't see the valley.)
What's going on?
(The road looks a bit creepy.)
Thank you for driving us.
- Thank you.
My gosh. Let's get out of the car.
(They've arrived.)
(They came to the valley, recommended by the elders.)
- My gosh.
- Come on out.
(No matter how hard they look, they can't see the valley.)
Wait. There's a valley here?
(Did we come to the right spot?)
No way.
(They head into the forest.)
This place is...
(When they go in a little more...)
I can hear the water.
(It's secretly tucked away deep in the forest.)
(The valley is surrounded by dense trees.)
(Clean valley water flowing from the deep heart of Mount Jiri)
(Full of big and small rocks, perfect for resting up)
This is spectacular.
It looks like AI-generated.
(The view takes their breath away.)
(The valley cools them down to the bone.)
(Let's have a blast here.)
Now that I'm here, I love it.
I want to go in the water now that I'm here.
(Jin Hee already comes down to the valley.)
(He rolls up his pants right away.)
(He starts carrying the watermelon.)
Are you going to put it in there?
(Must-have fruit, watermelon chilled in the cool valley water)
(Sun Young comes down to the valley next.)
My gosh! This is great!
(Dancing a jig out of sheer joy)
(Laughing)
Did you bring clothes, Sun Young?
- No.
- What are you going to do?
It's all right.
I can wrap a towel around me and get in the car.
(She's getting ready to enter the water already.)
(She dips her feet in first.)
(Screaming)
It's cold.
It's so cold.
(The stream is freezing cold.)
(You Seok follows her into the water.)
Gosh. It's cold.
It's cool.
(He adapts to it right away.)
It's nice and cold.
(A refreshing chill reaches all the way to her head.)
It doesn't feel cold at all after a bit.
It feels freezing only at first.
(They get in the refreshing water one by one.)
You can't swim, can you, Jung Ah?
I'm afraid of water.
I'm generally scared of water.
(She's just going to watch others.)
I'm going in.
Really?
(Dipping)
(Sun Young's sitting in the water.)
(Laughing)
(She's having the most fun after saying she would never go in.)
- It's so cold.
- Be careful.
(You Seok, who wanted to come to the stream the most, )
(dives into the water.)
(Swimming)
(He feels at home.)
He's floating.
(He's one with the water.)
(He checks underwater while he's at it.)
The water is so clear that I can see underwater.
I can see everything.
- I love it.
- Do you?
- It's so lovely.
- It's cold.
It's great.
(This is the joy of summer.)
This side is deep. Gosh. It's deep.
(Sun Young is in the water before long.)
(They enjoy the day, )
(not worrying about their clothes getting wet.)
(The youngest one is having a blast with the water gun.)
(Target spotted. Attack!)
(Bang, bang)
(Struggling, giggling)
(Giggling)
(Are you done?)
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
(A sense of dread creeps in.)
(Please hold this for a second, Sun Young.)
No!
(Time for revenge!)
(Getting way more in return)
(Glancing)
It's over now.
(She's taking a total loss.)
(And...)
Wait. Hold on.
(Sun Young is getting splashed from both sides.)
- Come on.
- It's because of the water bottle.
The water bottle.
What is this?
(Soaking wet)
(Round 2 begins right away.)
- Hey.
- Gosh.
(Unlike the energetic younger ones, )
Stop coming at me.
(she's cowering to avoid getting splashed.)
- Sun Young.
- Yes?
- Let's go somewhere deeper.
- Where?
- It's shallow here.
- Let me get used to it first.
Give me a second.
I need to get used to the temperature.
I'm old, You Seok.
Hold on.
(I'm Sun Young, and I'm 50.)
(Come hang with us.)
(Gasping)
(Are you really going to join us?)
(Jin Hee quietly joins them.)
- Did you just splash me, Jin Hee?
- No.
No, they did it.
(Splashing)
(This is payback!)
Goodness.
(Wet)
You started it.
He put his cap on backward.
- I wanted to try this.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- I wanted to try it.
(He grabs the water gun.)
Hold on.
(Firing away)
I knew it.
(Screaming)
Hey, stop.
(Unleashing on Sun Young after taking out Yoon Seo)
(Laughing)
It's hilarious.
(Hey!)
Jin Hee.
(There's no mercy when he has the water gun.)
(One water gun makes him happier than ever.)
Are you getting ready to get back?
(2-on-1 revenge begins.)
(Giving it her all)
(Wobbling)
(Yes! We won.)
I'm scared.
(Seeing them enjoy the water makes You Seok proud.)
(Since he's already wet, Jin Hee wears the goggles...)
(and starts diving.)
(Submerging his whole body in the cold mountain stream)
That's crazy.
(Refreshing just to watch)
There are minnows underwater.
(The water is so clear that they can spot minnows.)
Hey!
(They return to childhood and enjoy a fun day in the water.)
It's been years since I came to a mountain stream.
- I can't even remember when.
- Me neither. I love it.
Yes. I love it too.
(This is a real paradise.)
Can I borrow your tube?
(You Seok borrows the tube suddenly.)
Why? What are you going to do?
I'm going to try something fun.
(He sits between the rocks where the water gathers.)
(Getting into position)
(Go.)
(He starts drifting down the current.)
(Floating)
(Exhilarated)
He's back.
(Amazed)
There is a rapid we can ride.
It's a water slide.
(Excited)
(Go.)
(Screaming)
(Sliding down excitedly while screaming like a dolphin)
(Giggling)
(It's so much fun.)
(I need to capture this.)
(Leisurely drifting along, kicking her feet)
Gosh. That was lovely.
(Then she parks herself perfectly.)
(Flashing a V-sign)
(Excited)
(Jin Hee goes to try it himself.)
(Shocked)
(The current is faster than he thought.)
(Amazed)
(After cheering himself up, )
(off he goes.)
(Amazed)
(Laughing)
(He's super excited.)
(Amazed)
(Happy)
(It's hilarious.)
(Drifting down with a happy smile on his face)
(Dopamine overload)
(Another dopamine addict can relate to him.)
(Her hair is all messy.)
- Wait. Your hair.
- What?
What happened to it?
(I'll protect her at all costs.)
(Stroking)
(She's stroking her hair like a mother.)
(After taking care of her sister, )
(she's back at being the youngest.)
(Loving it)
Look at me, Sun Young.
Give me a V.
(Flashing a V-sign)
(She's cute.)
(Sun Young seems especially childlike today.)
Are you asking for my hand?
(Are you asking for my hand?)
(She even grabs her hand.)
(You Seok grabs the watermelon he put in the water in advance.)
I caught...
a watermelon...
(A watermelon off the mountain stream)
in the water.
(Jung Ah cuts the watermelon.)
(Splitting)
(The watermelon is red and ripe.)
Gosh. That's amazing.
(That looks really good.)
(She cuts the ripe watermelon into pieces.)
It was so much fun.
(Everyone enjoys a piece.)
What? Why is it so sweet?
- It's so good.
- It's like...
(Super sweet)
(It's better after being chilled in the cold stream.)
I love it so much after playing in the water.
(Taking in summer with her whole body)
If I knew I'd have fun like this, I would've taken some carbs.
I'm out of energy like an elementary school child.
Did you have that much fun?
- Yes.
- You gave it all.
You played with your all might.
It was so much fun.
I'm so glad you insisted on coming here.
- See, Sun Young?
- Since we got here,
Shouldn't you come when I ask you to?
Today was the most fun.
Actually, seeing you enjoying it so much...
makes me happy.
To see you happy like this.
It suddenly reminds me of my elementary school days.
- I'm choked.
- Everyone feels the same.
I remember how it felt after playing in the water.
- Is that how you feel right now?
- Yes.
Since then...
I know why I feel like that.
I haven't played in the water without my kid.
You never went to a place for you to play.
It was for your daughter.
(Since she became a mother, she has always put her child first.)
(The moment she was simply herself, not a mother)
It's crazy.
(Choking up)
I'm sad, Sun Young.
- I'm choked.
- Right.
(Emotional)
- That's funny.
- Right.
(Today, she played without a worry...)
I had no idea why I was so excited.
(like she did in her childhood.)
I had no idea.
(Teary)
So, you don't like your kid?
(What was that?)
(Jin Hee, a T-type)
You don't want your child to tag along.
(Wasn't that what you meant?)
(Killing the vibe)
(She's basically sobbing.)
(It's sad yet funny.)
(It's funny yet sad.)
You got busted, didn't you?
That's why you're laughing.
(Jin Hee joked to comfort her.)
(What's wrong with her hair again?)
(Come on, Sun Young.)
(Stroking)
I got really choked up.
- Me too.
- But to cry in this situation...
- I got choked up too.
- was very weird.
Kim Sun Young was here to enjoy the fun.
- I got emotional too.
- Right.
Is this their thing?
They're always whispering to each other.
(A Type T can't understand the world of Type F.)
I don't know why they do that.
She understands how I feel...
whereas you, Jung Ah, never get what I say.
Yoon Seo gets me.
I told you.
Taking a child can be burdensome.
- You need to take care of her.
- Who wants more watermelon?
- When you take care of them...
- Have some more.
I'm so full...
- because I've been eating so much.
- Right.
(Type T and Type F are all talking to themselves.)
Let's go now. Let's hurry back.
(Crawling)
- What is she doing?
- Let's go now.
Let's hurry back.
Now, Jin Hee is telling her off.
She gets a red card.
- A red card.
- A red one.
(Here.)
(The happy outing in the water comes to an end.)
Let's go.
Let's go to our next spot.
(Located in Pyeongsa-ri, Agyang-myeon, Hadong-gun..)
(is the House of Choi Champan, the setting of the novel "Toji.")
(From Pyeongsa-ri to town, )
(ox carts and woodcutters...)
(travel 12km along the river.)
(Woodcutters and farmers said hello to Choi Chi Su.)
(Excerpt from "Toji" by Pak Kyong Ni)
(It's one of the main settings of "Toji,")
(a novel by Park Kyong Ni.)
(Also, many periodic dramas were shot here.)
(You can see the foothills of Mount Jiri and the Seomjin River.)
(Mount Jiri, Seomjin River)
(It's a must-stop when you're in Hadong.)
It's so pretty here.
Look at the view of Mount Jiri.
(Mount Jiri welcomes them from the moment they arrive.)
This village is huge.
- The House of Choi Champan.
- It's huge.
(They recreated the houses of Choi Champan and tenant farmers.)
- It's crazy.
- It's huge.
(The thatched houses belong to the tenant farmers.)
(This grand house is the House of Choi Champan.)
(Looking around)
- Come.
- Why?
- Let me take a photo.
- They'll take a photo.
(A spot for photos in the corner of the yard)
(The younger ones take their spots side by side.)
One, two, three.
(Winking)
How can they look so good?
- Go to the other one too.
- The other one too?
(Mom never misses a good photo spot.)
(They're a young master and a young lady this time.)
One, two, three.
(How adorable!)
- You were a young master.
- I made a face of a young master.
(Choi Champan's tough Master Roh and shy Lady Kang)
(Where do they head next?)
- Goodness.
- This is so nice.
(Amazed)
(Shocked)
- It's awesome.
- Yes.
(Passing through the grand gates between the quarters, )
(you can see the panoramic view of the vast Pyeongsa-ri Field.)
- It's amazing.
- What?
(The Couple Pines stand together in the middle of the field.)
I'm in awe when I look at the trees.
- A little.
- Right?
- It's awesome.
- This is awesome.
- Let's take a photo here.
- Yes, let's do that.
One, two, three.
(A family photo in Pyeongsa-ri Field with Jin Hee)
I want to have a hot bowl of gukbap.
- Something hot.
- And some jeon.
Nice.
It's a traditional pub.
(Toji Market's traditional pub is open.)
Can we get seafood pajeon with spicy chilis?
- Yes, you can.
- We can cook it right away.
- And one bibim guksu.
- The spicy noodles.
- Yes. Make it warm.
- Then it's bibim guksu,
- pajeon, and gukbap.
- And gukbap.
- Yes.
- Yes. And one makgeolli.
- One makgeolli.
- Yes.
- It'll be right up.
- Okay.
Thank you.
(They sit on a cool wooden platform.)
It's awesome.
(Amazed)
Did you order makgeolli?
(Chilled makgeolli is served right away.)
We'll drink here.
- You can drive.
- Sure. I'll drive.
Gosh. We have no choice but to drink.
We have no choice. We have to drink it.
I was going to drive.
Please don't.
- Good job.
- Yes.
Nice work.
(They gulp down the refreshing drink.)
(Satisfied)
It's so good. It's very clean.
(It's very clean.)
(It's so refreshing she can feel it all over.)
I think it tastes better because it's not carbonated.
It's so good. It's very clean.
(Gulping)
(It suits the youngest's palate too.)
Pajeon is ready already.
- You're right.
- It's ready.
(Their food is finally here.)
- You need to grab the drinks first.
- That was fast.
(Seafood pajeon with spicy chilis)
(It includes lots of fresh seafood and spicy chilis.)
(Bibim guksu seasoned with sweet and sour sauce)
(Beef gukbap to warm their stomachs)
(A feast at the traditional pub...)
(to fill their bellies after a day in the water)
(They are amazed by the visuals.)
- It looks so good.
- I can't believe it.
- Have some jeon.
- Have some pajeon, Jung Ah.
Okay.
(Jin Hee grabs hot gukbap first.)
These green onions are fresh.
(Slurping)
(He tries the soup first.)
(Savoring)
(Licking the spoon)
(He drinks straight from the bowl this time.)
The weather was perfect too.
(Its richness clears his stomach.)
(Sun Young tries the chunks in gukbap first.)
This place...
has amazing gukbap.
- This is a great gukbap spot.
- Yes.
(The spicy broth is loaded with hearty chunks.)
It's so good. This gukbap.
I'll tear it.
(Yoon Seo goes after pajeon.)
(Tearing apart)
It's good.
(She takes a big bite after dipping it in soy sauce.)
It's tasty.
(Satisfied)
- This pajeon is legit.
- Yes. It's legit.
It's crazy.
(Taking a bite)
(Satisfied)
- It's good.
- It's jeon.
It's amazing.
(Taking a sip of makgeolli)
(Taking a bite of pajeon)
This makgeolli is incredible.
(The combination that never fails you)
(They're filling their empty bellies...)
(after having fun in the water.)
(Happy)
(She's enjoying it.)
(Chewing)
(They can't stop eating because it's so good.)
(Everyone enjoys the meal after the fun in the water.)
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- This is what happiness is.
This is true happiness.
(It's a day of pure happiness.)
While I was shooting,
I thought my daughter would love to come here.
- I thought of my husband and kids.
- Right.
We can eat here too.
- My daughter loves these.
- Right.
You have to go further up.
No matter where I go, all I can think of is my daughter.
That's right.
- Do you like your daughter?
- Yes.
(He's still suspicious.)
- She loves her daughter?
- Really? I'm glad to hear that.
(Laughing)
I wasn't going to have kids.
I didn't care about them.
- But...
- I didn't really like them either.
(Jin Hee wasn't fond of babies.)
But you had kids.
After having them, they allow me to feel...
a new kind of sensation and emotion.
(They grew even closer while talking to one another.)
(On their way back)
(Showing his phone all of a sudden)
- What is it?
- Jung Ah.
- It's Eun Jin.
- Where are you?
- What?
- Hello.
- Is this a video call?
Yes. Eun Jin.
- Jung Ah.
- Yes.
- How have you been?
- Good.
What did you do today?
- We caught eels today.
- It was so hard.
They weren't the pike eels we had before.
They were freshwater eels.
- They were wild freshwater eels.
- Wild eels.
- Freshwater eels?
- Yes.
It was so tough.
- Aren't those the strong ones?
- Totally.
When we grabbed them, they slipped away.
You were brave like always.
I'm not a brave one.
Eun Jin is scared of those.
- I watched everything.
- I'm afraid of fish.
- She's terrified of fish.
- I watched the whole thing.
I watched every episode Eun Jin was in.
- Yes.
- I watched them.
- See you soon.
- It feels like seeing a celebrity.
Exactly. It's crazy.
I really want to thank you.
After You Seok joined the show,
- he became his old self again.
- I see.
He's more cheerful now, right?
He's way more cheerful.
- Really?
- I recently met with him.
- He went, "Eun Jin."
- "Eun Jin."
(You Seok has become adorable since he joined the show.)
He acts really cute.
- I can see him smiling.
- Yes.
Do you have a guest?
Yes. Ji Jin Hee is here today,
and he's driving right now.
Hello, Jin Hee.
- Jin Hee, Eun Jin says hello.
- Hello.
He's driving.
Anyway, stay healthy and be strong.
- "Be strong."
- Gosh, Eun Jin.
- It's just
- Amazing - "Anyway."
- Bye, everyone.
- Bye, Eun Jin.
- Bye.
(Eun Jin and the siblings say goodbye.)
Eun Jin always says,
"It's just... It's super..."
It was delicious.
It was delicious. And I had so much fun today.
And thanks to you driving, Jin Hee,
- That's right.
- we get to drink.
That's right. Thank you.
Jin Hee is a reliable type.
Yes.
- I felt it today.
- Do you know what I'm saying?
- His very presence is comforting.
- Totally.
- Yes.
I know what you're saying.
You made us feel comfortable,
so thank you.
- Acting this cute...
- Thank you.
Gets a green card.
Green.
And he suddenly goes, "Red."
- "I'm feeling uncomfortable."
- Hey.
Green.
(His actual reaction: Green)
It's green.
(Just like Jin Hee in a refreshing green mood, )
- Isn't this road pretty?
- It's cool.
It's so pretty, isn't it?
- How are these trees so big?
- It's prettier under the sun.
(they drive through the tunnel of green trees.)
- I love Hadong.
- I love it.
I love Hadong.
- I like Hadong.
- Yes.
(The siblings in Hadong are in a green mood too.)
(They drive along the road they've gotten familiar with...)
(and reached the town where the Siblings' House is.)
- You must be tired.
- No, I'm fine.
- Liar.
- I got some sleep.
Stop lying. You're tired.
Gosh, it's already evening.
- Fresh...
- Off the Sea.
That was great.
(They still have a good cheer.)
That was amazing.
I'll go get changed quickly.
(Groaning)
(Drowsy)
(They all plop down as soon as they get home.)
(Captain Yum is the only one standing among them.)
(Approaching slowly)
(She goes straight to the kitchen storage.)
(We had plenty of fun, so we should cook now.)
(Grunting)
(Everyone gets up at the sound of Captain Yum's wake-up call.)
What shall I do?
(Everyone gathers at the military training ground.)
- Gosh. We caught eels today.
- Yes.
So you can make grilled eels...
with You Seok.
(That sounds delicious.)
(Screaming)
(They worked hard...)
(to catch fresh wild eels.)
(They're going to have a hearty amount of grilled eels.)
Look at the eels.
(Delicious and rare wild eel party, coming soon)
- You Seok, start a fire.
- Yes.
- All right.
(Sniffing)
I can smell other places starting a fire.
(The neighbors happen to be preparing for dinner as well.)
(What kind of dinner are the Maegye Village neighbors making?)
(Yoo Yoon Oh's house)
(First male chef on Fresh off the Sea)
This is freshwater eel.
It tastes different because the water is clean.
It smells different too.
If you use hinoki...
to start a fire, it smells really nice too.
(Boil it for 1 hour over a hinoki wood fire with a good scent.)
Then throw away the bones.
(The eel meat and the bones are infused into the broth, )
Then I make eel soup with the broth.
(so the broth is milky and rich.)
(Then add various seasoned vegetables...)
(like taro stems, butterbur stems, bracken, and mung bean sprouts.)
(Add blended chili...)
(and perilla seed powder.)
(Then the thick and savory soup will be ready.)
(The spicy eel soup makes you crave rice...)
(as soon as you see it.)
And I make a pancake.
(Another secret weapon dish)
(It has plenty of marsh clams...)
(from the clear Seomjin River.)
(Marsh clam chive pancake that's extremely savory)
Gwangyang is famous for its plums.
(A meal filled with ingredients in season...)
(from the Seomjin River side)
Let's get to work.
Why do people have to keep working?
(Laughing)
I wonder about that too.
- You're sleepy, right?
- I'm quite sleepy.
- Because we were in the water.
- Yes. We worked a lot too.
Where should I place this?
Shall we? All right.
- Jin Hee has great stamina. Right?
- I know.
I envy that.
- I'm really envious.
- Me too.
(Hitting)
- He's so strong too.
- I wish I could be too.
- Right?
- What are you doing?
We were saying we should work hard.
All right. Hurry up and get to work. What are you doing? It's started.
(Glaring)
(Smiling)
- Great.
- I fell for it.
(Forgiving since he's cute)
All right.
I love you
(After flirting with Yoon Seo, )
(the one in charge of a fire gets ready to start one right away.)
(Relaxed)
(Take out the charcoal from the bag.)
(Lighting the torch right away)
I can start a fire in five minutes. It's totally doable.
(He starts the fire confidently.)
(Before we know it, )
(the promised five minutes have passed.)
(How is the fire?)
You can start one in no time?
- Isn't there one more?
- Sorry?
You can start it in no time?
(Charcoal sitting quietly without a single flame)
Actually, it's my first time starting a fire with charcoal.
- I've always used firewood.
- Gosh. That's bad.
Come to think of it, I've...
I've only used firewood.
Charcoal takes a long time.
(Starting a fire with charcoal is on another level.)
(The fire fairy, Jin Hee, sets off to help.)
Gosh.
(Surprised)
It's okay.
(Manly)
(Heating the charcoal with intense flames)
All right.
Then fan it to make the fire stronger.
(Fan it to add your wish to make the fire stronger.)
(Starting a fire with charcoal comes true.)
(The charcoal fire has started perfectly, )
(thanks to the fire fairy, Jin Hee.)
Are the eels in the fridge?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(After clearing the mission of starting a charcoal fire, )
(he sets off to get the wild eels.)
Gosh.
(Amazed)
Eels. Yes.
Gosh, it doesn't have any bad odor.
- Really?
- Yes.
It doesn't smell bad at all.
(Uncle Jin Hee is thrilled.)
Even if you scrape it,
- there is no mucus.
- There isn't?
There's none. It's amazing.
(He means it's clean without any mucus.)
Gosh.
- This is incredible.
- It really is.
- It's seriously amazing.
- It's really amazing.
(It's even fresher as they caught it from the sea.)
- Gosh, the eel is huge.
- It's wonderful.
It really is wonderful.
(Plump and appetizing)
Gosh, this is amazing.
It doesn't smell bad at all. It's fascinating.
Seeing it flattened like this...
- It's incredible.
- The folded one is one.
(If you spread the wild eel inside the bag, )
(it fills the entire gridiron.)
- This is really amazing.
- Right.
(Everyone is enjoying the wonderful wild eels.)
(Putting the thick wild eels on the gridiron...)
(and placing it over the charcoal fire right away.)
- Shall we use both sides?
- Yes.
Here.
(Placing lots of plump wild eel)
(Sprinkling salt gently)
The salt pops because of the fire. Be careful.
(It's guaranteed to be delicious.)
You can sprinkle plenty. It'll fall anyway.
You built a good fire.
(While a work of art is being made...)
Next, I will...
If I start making napa cabbage soup first...
For napa cabbage soup, I just need to make a broth,
add napa cabbage and doenjang.
- Then how...
- Add garlic too.
I should add seasoning powder bag first.
(Sun Young is making a soup on her own?)
(Actually, Sun Young has been...)
(Jung Ah!)
(Ma'am?)
(She's only assisted Captain Yum for the main dish.)
(She's making a main dish for the first time today.)
(They're going to have refreshing napa cabbage soup...)
(with grilled wild eels.)
Shall we look for the seasoning powder bag together?
Yes.
Two.
Two?
(Cooking with viewers? Is she...)
(Kim Sun Young's Best Cooking Secrets)
(Today's menu, doenjang napa cabbage soup)
Shall we make it in the pretty green pot?
A really pretty green pot.
(She chose a pretty pot.)
Broth.
Let's make a broth with the seasoning powder bag.
(Add a seasoning powder bag and boil it.)
Isn't the pot too small?
She told me to make just a little.
- Just a little...
- But that's way too small.
(Returning to Fresh off the Sea with generous Captain Yum)
- This is small?
- Yes, we have that much cabbage.
There's quite a lot.
(Piled)
(Ms. Kim Sun Young has hit a roadblock as soon as she started.)
This is small?
We're making more than this?
All right. I got it.
Shall we make it in a bigger pot?
(Today's menu, doenjang napa cabbage soup in a large quantity)
(Making a mistake right away)
(Making a fuss)
(It's not easy to make a main dish for the first time.)
This big?
(Added 2L of water as it's in a large quantity)
The fire isn't on.
(Even the fire is off too?)
- The fire isn't on.
The fire isn't on?
(Infusing the seasoning bag in cold water)
That's a lot of water.
I can boil it with the lid open. It'll boil down.
(Gulping)
Jung Ah! Are anchovy broth...
and anchovy sauce different?
Yes, they're totally different.
- Don't bring anchovy broth.
- Okay.
Anchovy sauce...
Premium anchovy... Sand lance sauce?
Where is the anchovy sauce?
(Will Sun Young be able to make napa cabbage soup?)
(Captain Yum is preparing glutinous rice.)
(Pouring rice)
(While deciding menus for Eat Together yesterday morning, )
(Jung Ah thought of yakbab.)
(Yakbab? That's incredible.)
(They'll make yakbab for dessert.)
(I'm good at making yakbab.)
(As it takes a long time, she'll make it a day before.)
(Yoon Seo was highly looking for it too.)
(Jung Ah starts making yakbab...)
(in bulk.)
(Emptying it out)
(It's more than just a huge batch of yakbab.)
(It's 40 servings of yakbab.)
(Even Captain Yum hasn't made this much yakbab in one go.)
(The biggest batch of yakbab you've ever seen)
(40 servings of glutinous rice)
(Over 30 jujubes)
- We don't need to rinse pine nuts.
- And the pumpkin seeds.
(Two bags of pumpkin seeds)
This is a lot.
Well, this is enough for 40 people.
More ingredients mean deeper flavor.
I'll cut these and give them a light rinse.
(Adding over 70 chestnuts)
(A crazy amount of ingredients for the biggest batch of food)
(Will she be able to manage this like the generous cook she is?)
(Slicing them finely to make it easier for elders to eat)
(Slicing 1 jujube)
(She slices each one with utmost care.)
(But there's one problem.)
(She has to do this over 30 times.)
(And that's only for jujubes.)
(She's slicing the jujubes nonstop...)
(in the same pose.)
(She's been at this for some time now.)
(But she still has a pile of jujubes to slice.)
(Sniffling)
Oh, my back.
(She faces the hardship of making 40 servings with jujubes.)
Hold on. Why is my neck so sore?
- Your neck is sore?
- Yes.
(She ends up with a cervical disc herniation.)
(Is she finally done?)
(As if. She has to slice 40 servings of chestnuts too.)
My back hurts.
(She's out of it.)
(Worried)
We need to cut them into quarters?
- This... No, not into quarters.
- Okay.
- I see. Like that.
- This big.
(No matter how exhausting it is, she cuts them into small pieces.)
- Should I do this?
- Cut them like this. Yes.
- Then give them a gentle rinse.
- Sure.
(They finally switch places.)
These chestnuts will taste great in yakbab.
(Let me get started now.)
(Yoon Seo, the art major, )
(neatly slices the chestnuts.)
(Meanwhile, Sun Young's broth has developed a rich flavor.)
I'll add the napa cabbages.
(She adds the napa cabbages to the doenjang broth.)
(She grabs a handful of the cabbages...)
(and adds them to the broth.)
(She's adding another handful?)
(A pile of napa cabbages)
This is too much.
It's too much.
(She's a generous cook just like Jung Ah.)
It's more than I thought.
(But more ingredients mean richer flavor.)
(How will her generous napa cabbage soup turn out?)
- Here's a fan.
- Great.
Fan it gently like this.
(We need a good wind for this masterpiece.)
(The wild eels are getting grilled nicely over charcoal.)
Have you ever seen a Japanese master grill eel?
- They fan the fire all day.
- This is how they look at the eel.
- Seriously.
- Like this. I'm serious.
The way they handle the fan is different.
- Yes, that's it.
- Right.
(He suddenly starts dancing with the fan.)
That's how they snapped their wrist.
The masterful wrist snap.
(This is the wrist snap of an eel master.)
Eels.
(Laughing)
It's like he's done this before. He looks like a real eel master.
(Channeling his inner eel master way too hard)
(He fans the fire and grills one side like a master.)
Now.
(Groaning)
(He confidently flips it over.)
(How does it look?)
It's not cooked at all.
- We should give it more time.
- It's not cooked.
It's white now. Right?
(The flesh of the wild eel is still milky white.)
(He quickly flips it back.)
(Meowing)
Oh, my.
(It still looks tasty.)
Does it smell good?
So cute.
(Dashing over)
The neighborhood cats are going wild.
These eels are going to drive them nuts.
(As the wild eels sizzle to a golden brown, )
(the neighborhood cats start gathering.)
(Meowing)
- Oh, no. They want some.
- They want food.
Look at that one. It's sitting down politely.
They're talking to each other.
(Please give us one eel.)
But we can't give you our eels.
We have to eat them.
I'm sorry. We can't give you eels.
(Because we worked so hard to catch them.)
(Precious)
(He flips the grill net.)
(Amazed)
My gosh.
Yours looks golden brown too.
(Proud)
(Cheerfully humming)
(Golden brown)
- This side looks better.
- Yes. It's grilled nicely.
(Appetizing)
Look at the meat.
(They can't help but marvel at the fatty meat.)
(Drawn to the eels by the smell)
This is a lot of work.
- This looks amazing.
- It does.
I want to look too.
(Amazed)
(Jaw-dropping)
Look how thick it is.
Awesome.
(Thick)
This looks so good.
Gosh, this is no joke.
- Look how thick that is.
- This looks so good.
(Masterpiece)
- This is...
- It smells amazing.
(Their third labor, green plum)
(Only three of them will go.)
(The one going home...)
(versus the ones going to the green plum field)
(A mind game with their fate on the line)
(A sip can result in death.)
(Only the one with the right pick...)
(can smile.)
(Which three will go work on the green plum field tomorrow?)
(A voice resonates throughout the village in Hadong.)
(Is that Jung Ah's voice?)
(Serving 40 residents of the village)
(A project for Jung Ah to level up from generous to bountiful)
(They're running out of time.)
(They're short-handed too.)
(They're lacking willpower as well.)
(Jung Ah is about to lose it.)
(There's no time to waste now.)
(Remaining time)
(Only 5 minutes)
(Instead of water, )
(it's their heart simmering over the flame.)
(We can't do a half-hearted job.)
(The elders of the village...)
(will flood in soon.)
(The biggest mission of the season)
(Will the siblings be able to complete Eat Together?)